Finding Aid for the Los Angeles Daily News Negatives, 1925-1954
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 1950
  - Street scene in Chavez Ravine, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1950; Neg. # 52406-1 (Box 156)
  - Bridge in Chavez Ravine's "Lil' Town", 1950; Neg. # 52406-2 (Box 156)
  - Mayor Fletcher Bowron proclaims Negro History Week in Los Angeles (Calif.), February 1950; Neg. # 49508 (Box 147)
- 1951
  - Street scene in Chavez Ravine, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1951; Neg. # 52400-1 (Box 156)
  - Home in Chavez Ravine, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1951; Neg. # 52402-1 (Box 156)
  - Land use inspection in Chavez Ravine, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1951; Neg. # 52404-1 (Box 156)
- 1952
  - Adoptions in Los Angeles, California, ca. 1952; Neg. # 54847 (Box 163)
  - Art Aragon rests after a fight, ca. 1952; Neg. # 55083 (Box 163)
  - Mayor Fletcher Bowron, Marian Anderson, and the Reverend Baxter Duke, ca. 1952; Neg. # 55602-1 (Box 165)
  - Undocumented Mexican workers eat a meal before deportation, 1952; Neg. # 56065 (Box 167)
  - Mayor Fletcher Bowron celebrates Cinco de Mayo, ca. 1952; Neg. # 56287 (Box 167)
- 1953
  - Hillside view of Chavez Ravine, ca. 1953; Neg. # 51214 (Box 152)
  - Home in Chavez Ravine, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1953; Neg. # 51214-1 (Box 152)
  - Hillside view of Chavez Ravine, ca. 1953; Neg. # 51214-2 (Box 152)
  - Hillside view of Chavez Ravine, ca. 1953; Neg. # 51214-3 (Box 152)
  - Dragon costume for New Year festivities in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1953; Neg. # 58550-1 (Box 176)
  - Preparing for New Year festivities in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1953; Neg. # 58550-3 (Box 176)
  - View of the Plaza looking towards Union Station, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1953; Neg. # 58845-11 (Box 177)
  - Old Mission Plaza Church, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1953; Neg. # 58845-2 (Box 177)
  - Watts Towers, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1953; Neg. # 58871 (Box 177)
  - Simon Rodia and his Watts Towers, portrait, ca. 1953; Neg. # 58871-1 (Box 177)
  - Watts Towers, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1953; Neg. # 58871-2 (Box 177)
  - Undocumented Mexican workers arrested in rail yard, 1953; Neg. # 60963 (Box 181)
  - Undocumented Mexican workers arrested in rail yard, 1953; Neg. # 60963-2 (Box 181)
  - Nisei festival queens pose with flowers in Little Tokyo, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1953; Neg. # 61029 (Box 181)
  - Tenement house in Los Angeles (Calif.), 1953; Neg. # 61179-1 (Box 182)
  - Tenement house in Los Angeles (Calif.), 1953; Neg. # 61179-2 (Box 182)
  - Ashley L. Totten, George Meany, and Randolph A. Philip, ca. 1953; Neg. # 61600 (Box 183)
- 1954
  - Kites in a Chinatown shop, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1954; Neg. # 62048 (Box 185)
  - Leroy Paige, portrait, 1954; Neg. # 62667 (Box 187)
  - Undocumented Mexican workers await deportation, 1954; Neg. # 63891-1 (Box 192)
  - Undocumented Mexican workers board buses for deportation, 1954; Neg. # 63891-2 (Box 192)
  - Undocumented Mexican worker awaits deportation, 1954; Neg. # 63891-4 (Box 192)
  - Moon festival lantern parade in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1954; Neg. # 69395-1 (Box 192)
  - Moon festival lantern parade in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1954; Neg. # 69395-3 (Box 194)
  - Moon festival lantern parade in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1954; Neg. # 69395-4 (Box 194)